let questions = [
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time top scorer in Premier League history?",
    a: "Thierry Henry",
    b: "Wayne Rooney",
    c: "Alan Shearer",
    d: "Sergio Agüero",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team holds the record for the most Premier League titles?",
    a: "Arsenal",
    b: "Liverpool",
    c: "Man United",
    d: "Man City",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who won the Premier League Golden Boot for the 2022-2023 season?",
    a: "Mohamed Salah",
    b: "Harry Kane",
    c: "Erling Haaland",
    d: "Son Heung-min",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which club famously went unbeaten throughout the entire 2003-2004 Premier League season?",
    a: "Liverpool",
    b: "Chelsea",
    c: "Manchester United",
    d: "Arsenal",
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the manager of Manchester City as of 2023?",
    a: "Jürgen Klopp",
    b: "José Mourinho",
    c: "Ole Gunnar Solskjær",
    d: "Pep Guardiola",
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most Premier League assists in a single season?",
    a: "Kevin De Bruyne",
    b: "Frank Lampard",
    c: "Cesc Fàbregas",
    d: "Thierry Henry",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Which stadium is the home of Arsenal FC?",
    a: "Old Trafford",
    b: "Anfield",
    c: "Stamford Bridge",
    d: "Emirates Stadium",
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the youngest goalscorer in Premier League history?",
    a: "James Vaughan",
    b: "Wayne Rooney",
    c: "Michael Owen",
    d: "Ryan Giggs",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team won the inaugural Premier League season in 1992-1993?",
    a: "Arsenal",
    b: "Manchester United",
    c: "Liverpool",
    d: "Leeds United",
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is known as the 'Special One' and managed Chelsea during two spells in the Premier League?",
    a: "José Mourinho",
    b: "Arsène Wenger",
    c: "Rafa Benítez",
    d: "Claudio Ranieri",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Which club is nicknamed the 'Red Devils'",
    a: "Liverpool",
    b: "Manchester City",
    c: "Manchester United",
    d: "Chelsea",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the captain of Liverpool FC as of 2023?",
    a: "Virgil van Dijk",
    b: "Mohamed Salah",
    c: "Andrew Robertson",
    d: "Trent Alexander-Arnold",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player famously scored a hat-trick in just 7 minutes for Southampton against Aston Villa in 2015?",
    a: "Jamie Vardy",
    b: "Sadio Mané",
    c: "Theo Walcott",
    d: "Harry Kane",
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most appearances in the Premier League?",
    a: "Steven Gerrard",
    b: "Frank Lampard",
    c: "Ryan Giggs",
    d: "Gareth Barry",
    answer: "d",
  },
];
